<?xml version='1.0'?>
<CARD_V2>
  <FILENAME text="VASTWOOD_GORGER_M13_196" />
  <CARDNAME text="VASTWOOD_GORGER" />
  <TITLE>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="en-US"><![CDATA[Vastwood Gorger]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="it-IT"><![CDATA[Ingoiatore di Boscovasto]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="de-DE"><![CDATA[Riesenholz-Verschlinger]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="fr-FR"><![CDATA[Avaleur de Vastebois]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="es-ES"><![CDATA[Insaciable del Bosque Extenso]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="jp-JA"><![CDATA[巨森を喰らうもの]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="ko-KR"><![CDATA[광활림의 대식가]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="ru-RU"><![CDATA[Проглот Широколесья]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="pt-BR"><![CDATA[Devorador de Matavasta]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
  </TITLE>
  <MULTIVERSEID value="M13_196" />
  <ARTID value="M13_196" />
  <ARTIST name="Kieran Yanner" />
  <CASTING_COST cost="{5}{G}" />
  <FLAVOURTEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="en-US"><![CDATA[“A long and difficult incision revealed  that all vital organs are housed in the head, save for a long chain of stomachs, forty in all, leading from its throat to the end of the tail.”
—Mulak Ffar, Vastwood Biodiversity]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="it-IT"><![CDATA[“Una lunga e laboriosa incisione ha rivelato che tutti gli organi vitali sono collocati nella testa, a parte una lunga catena di stomaci, quaranta in tutto, che parte dalla gola fino a raggiungere la punta della coda.”
—Mulak Ffar, Biodiversità di Boscovasto]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="de-DE"><![CDATA[„Ein langer und komplizierter Schnitt offenbarte, dass alle lebenswichtigen Organe im Kopf untergebracht sind, bis auf eine lange Kette aus Mägen. Derer gibt es insgesamt vierzig, die sich vom Schlund bis zum Ende des Schwanzes ziehen.”
—Mulak Ffar, Riesenholz-Artenvielfalt]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="fr-FR"><![CDATA[« Une incision laborieuse a révélé que tous les organes vitaux sont logés dans la tête à l’exception d’une longue chaîne d’estomacs, quarante en tout, allant de la gorge à l’extrémité de la queue. »
—Mulak Ffar, Biodiversité de Vastebois]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="es-ES"><![CDATA[“Una incisión larga y difícil reveló que todos los órganos vitales se alojan en la cabeza excepto por una larga cadena de estómagos, cuarenta en total, que van desde su garganta hasta el extremo de la cola.”
—Mulak Ffar, La biodiversidad del Bosque Extenso]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="jp-JA"><![CDATA[「長く困難な解剖の結果、主要器官がすべて頭部に集中していることが判明した。この他には長い胃（合計40個ある）が喉から尾の先まで連なっていた。」――ムーラク・ファー著『巨森の生物多様性』]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="ko-KR"><![CDATA[“길고 복잡한 절개선 속에서 드러난 것은 모든 주요 생체 기관이 머리 안에 있다는 것입니다. 단, 목구멍에서 꼬리까지는 연이어진 40개의 위가 있었습니다.”
—물락 파의 저서 광활림의 다양한 생물 중에서]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="ru-RU"><![CDATA[«В ходе тяжелого и продолжительного вскрытия выяснилось, что все жизненно важные органы расположены в голове, а от глотки до кончика хвоста идет длинная цепь из сорока желудков».
— Мулак Ффар, Фауна Широколесья]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
    <LOCALISED_TEXT LanguageCode="pt-BR"><![CDATA[“Uma longa e difícil incisão mostrou que todos os órgãos vitais estão alojados na cabeça, exceto por uma grande cadeia de estômagos, quarenta no total, que vai da garganta até o fim da cauda.”
— Mulak Ffar, Biodiversidade de Matavasta]]></LOCALISED_TEXT>
  </FLAVOURTEXT>
  <TYPE metaname="Creature" />
  <SUB_TYPE metaname="Wurm" />
  <EXPANSION value="M13" />
  <RARITY metaname="C" />
  <POWER value="5" />
  <TOUGHNESS value="6" />
  <SFX text="COMBAT_BITE_LARGE_ATTACK" power_boundary_min="4" power_boundary_max="-1" />
  <SFX text="COMBAT_BITE_SMALL_ATTACK" power_boundary_min="1" power_boundary_max="3" />
</CARD_V2>
